<resources>
    <string name="tfe_ic_app_name" translation_description="Image Classification demo app [CHAR_LIMIT=40]">Tomatix</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_camera_error" translation_description="Error regarding camera support[CHAR_LIMIT=40]">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_gpu_quant_error" translation_description="Error regarding GPU support for Quant models[CHAR_LIMIT=60]">GPU does not yet supported quantized models.</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_model" translatable="false">Model:</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string-array name="tfe_ic_models" translatable="false">
        <item>Quantized_EfficientNet</item>
        <item>Float_EfficientNet</item>
        <item>Quantized_MobileNet</item>
        <item>Float_MobileNet</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="blosom">Blosom End Rot</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_device" translatable="false">Device:</string>
    <string name="blosmo_cause">The conditions that cause blossom-end rot are closely linked to inconsistent soil moisture throughout the growing season. Since calcium is only moved into the plant with an ample moisture supply, when drought occurs the fruit continues to develop but will be affected by a calcium deficiency.</string>
    <string name="blosom_desc">Blossom-end rot first appears as water- soaked spots on the blossom end, or bottom, of the tomato. The affected tissue breaks down rapidly and the area becomes sunken, dark brown or black, and leathery. This can happen at any time as the tomatoes mature, and most often on the first tomatoes of the season.</string>
    <string name="blosom_prev">Grow tomatoes in well-drained soil high in organic matter with a soil pH between 6.5 and 7.5.</string>
    <string name="blosom_treatment"> Infected fruit should be removed when first noticed. This rot does not spread from plant to plant or from fruit to fruit, so even if it occurs on your earliest tomatoes, it may not affect later tomatoes on the same plant. Fungicides and insecticides are useless as control measures for this disorder.</string>
    <string name="anthracnose">Anthracnose</string>
    <string name="anthracnose_cause">Masses of pink to orange colored spores are released from these structures when weather is wet or humid. These spores are dispersed to other fruit by splashing water. Eventually the entire fruit will rot, especially when there are several anthracnose spots or decay organisms enter the diseased tissue. Fruit nearest to the ground are most likely to be affected. The fungus can also infect roots.</string>
    <string name="anthracnose_desc">Spots on fruit initially are small, circular, and depressed. They can enlarge considerably over time, and may develop concentric rings. The center of anthracnose spots become dark as the fungus produces spore-containing structures</string>
    <string name="anthracnose_prev">important practices for managing anthracnose is rotating where tomatoes are grown.</string>
    <string name="anthracnose_treatment"> Manage anthracnose by controlling sources of the pathogen, minimizing the opportunity for dispersal of the pathogen, reducing favorability of environmental conditions for disease development, and applying fungicides. There are no resistant varieties.</string>
    <string name="earlyblight">Eraly Blight</string>
    <string name="earlyblight_cause">Early blight can be caused by two different closely related fungi, Alternaria tomatophila and Alternaria solani.</string>
    <string name="earlyblight_desc">small dark spots form on older foliage near the ground.</string>
    <string name="earlyblight_prev">Fertilize properly to maintain vigorous plant growth. Particularly, do not over-fertilize with potassium and maintain adequate levels of both nitrogen and phosphorus</string>
    <string name="earlyblight_treatment"> It is important to alternate between different chemical families to avoid the development of pathogen insensitivity to particular active ingredients. Some insensitivity to the chemical family 11 has become more common in some areas, so particular care should be taken to rotate these with other chemical families.</string>

    <string name="fusarium">Fusarium wilt</string>
    <string name="fusarium_cause">Caused by  Fusarium wilt pathogen from infected seeds, soil blow or even the soil.</string>
    <string name="fusarium_desc">Wilting The plants will literally wilt. Often it starts with a single leaf or shoot, near the top of the plant. It will recover at night when temperatures are cooler, but as it progresses, the entire plant will wilt and not recover. Watering does not make a difference.</string>
    <string name="fusarium_prev">Apply lime to the soil in your garden, to bring the pH up into the neutral range of about 6.5 - 7.0.</string>
    <string name="fusarium_treatment"> This condition cannot be treatted but only managed.</string>
    <string name="fruit">It is at this stage that they need plenty of food – phosphorus and especially potash (potassium) to be exact. It is also at this stage that if they don’t receive enough calcium, Blossom End Rot is waiting to strike! Because calcium is an immobile nutrient, and doesn’t travel around a plant’s system freely, it is often easier to spray the leaves with calcium, which helps get it to where it is needed more quickly, than to hope for the best through the roots!</string>
    <string name="flower">It’s exciting to see flowers open because each one is a potential tomato! However, it is important to be aware of Blossom Drop – this happens when flowers fail to pollinate and the flower buds drop off the end of their stems.Stress can also cause plants to abort their flowers if they feel they cannot cope because of poor growing conditions or being over-watered or over-fed etc.</string>
    <string name="leaf">The leaf stage is when plants are developing both their roots and top growth. Nitrogen is the most important nutrient at this stage along with all the other elements in smaller amounts.</string>
    <string-array name="tfe_ic_devices" translatable="false">
        <item>CPU</item>
        <item>GPU</item>
        <item>NNAPI</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
